<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This is a customized copyright.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Can Black Pugs Cure Depression?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/eugene/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/eugene/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a quiet corner of the world, hidden from the bustling cities, there existed a secret research facility known only as The Pug Institute of Emotional Wellness. The scientists there were not your typical lab-coated academics—they were pug enthusiasts with a hunch that could change humanity forever. After years of observation, one thing became startlingly clear: black pugs were unlike any other animal on Earth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It all started with Dr. Penelope Fluffington, who noticed that every time a black pug waddled into her office, even the grumpiest postdoctoral researcher couldn’t help but smile. Their tiny wrinkled faces seemed to absorb sadness and exhale joy. Curious, she began a rigorous study, meticulously documenting the reactions of humans to pugs of every color. The results were undeniable: black pugs had a statistically significant effect on mood improvement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demon In Disguise</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ginette/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ginette/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At first glance, the Flame Point White Fluffy Cat looks like the epitome of innocence: a cloud of white fur with a little caramel blush on its ears, paws, and tail, eyes that could melt glaciers, and a purr that sounds like a tiny motorboat. The problem? That’s exactly what it wants you to think.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Behind those delicate whiskers and soft, marshmallowy fur lies a cunning mastermind of chaos. Studies (conducted entirely by suspiciously alarmed cat owners) reveal a shocking pattern: wherever this cat goes, destruction soon follows. A carefully placed glass of water on a counter? Gone. A newly folded pile of laundry? Fluffed, shredded, and strategically scattered. Your laptop keyboard? Consider it its personal scratching post.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
